https://www.myfoodandfamily.com/privacynotice#dontSellPersonalInfo

My Food and Family
A.1.
Kraft Heinz Site Privacy Notice
Kraft Heinz Site Privacy Notice For more information about your California Privacy Rights, please click here or scroll down. To opt out of the sale of your personal information, please click here or scroll down.
Effective Date: January 1, 2020 Your privacy is important to us. At The Kraft Heinz Company (“Kraft Heinz”), we recognize that visitors to our site may be concerned about the information they provide to us and how we handle that information. This Privacy Notice describes the types of information we collect from and about you when you visit any of our websites where this policy is posted (or the mobile optimized version of the website) (each a “Site”). This Privacy Notice also explains how we may use and disclose such information, as well as your ability to control certain uses of it. By using the Site, you agree to the collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Notice. If you do not, please do not use the Site. Information We Collect Information You Provide We collect certain personal information from you when you choose to share it with us. This may include when you use one of our Sites; register on one or more of our Sites; make a purchase; sign up for a newsletter or one of our email lists; use our services; participate in a contest, sweepstakes, game, survey, or promotion; request information from us; or otherwise contact us. The personal information we collect may include your name, birth date or age, telephone number, and e-mail address. If you purchase products or services from Kraft Heinz, we may also request your credit/debit card number or other financial information, along with billing information, so we can fulfill your order or request. We don’t require you to register or provide personal information to view our Sites or access much of its content, such as our many delicious recipes. However, you may be required to provide certain personal information to create a Site account, use certain features, or receive certain offers. For example, when you participate in certain interactive features on our Sites, such as using our recipe exchange, recipe ratings, and product ratings and reviews, you may also provide us with certain information like your e-mail address, nickname, city and state of residency, or submit content, such as recipes, ratings, comments, or pictures to the Site. In addition, we may give you the opportunity to tell your friends about certain features or information on our Sites. If you take advantage of our “Send to a Friend” option, we will ask you for your friend’s and your first name and e-mail addresses to send the information to them that you requested. We also offer visitors to our Sites various features for their enjoyment, which we may change from time to time. We may ask you to submit certain information so we can provide you with these features. If you use a third party login to create your account (such as Facebook Connect) or otherwise link to us, we may receive certain information about you from the third party (such as a social network) based on your registration and privacy settings on those third party websites. We may combine the information you provide to us with information from and about you that we automatically collect when you visit the Site, from third parties, or other online and offline sources. Information Collected By Automated Means We may use cookies, web beacons, pixel tags, log files, or local shared objects (such as Flash cookies), and other technologies to collect certain information about visitors to our Sites, use of our online services, and interactions with our emails and online advertisements, and to allow us to keep track of analytics and certain statistical information which enables us to improve the Sites and provide you with more relevant content and advertising on our Site and other sites. For example, through these means, we may automatically collect information such as your browser type, operating system, mobile device type and carrier, Internet service provider (“ISP”), and Internet Protocol (“IP”) address. We may also collect information about your use of and interaction with the Site, including as the webpages viewed, the date and time you visit the Site, the areas or pages of the Site that you visit, the amount of time you spend viewing or using the Site, the number of times you return to the Site, other click-stream or site usage data, whether you open, forward, or click-through links, emails, and ads, and other Site usage data. Collecting this information, and linking it with your personal information, for example, helps us to best tailor our website and enhance your online experience by saving your preferences while you are visiting a particular site, and to help identify site features, recipes, advertisements, and offers that may be of particular interest to you. When you view the site using a mobile device, in addition to the other information we may collect from your actions, we may collect your mobile phone number, device identifier, geolocation information, or device type and carrier. We also may use third party advertisements placed by ad networks to support our Sites. Some of these advertisers and ad networks may use technology such as cookies, web beacons, pixel tags, log files, or local shared objects (such as Flash cookies) when they advertise on our Site, which will also send these advertisers and ad networks non-personal information including your IP address, ISP, browser type, and whether you have Flash installed. Some of these advertisers and ad networks also may use anonymous data, such as demographic data, received from third parties to assist in the delivery of advertisements to you. These third-party advertisers and ad networks use the information described above to provide you relevant advertisements based on your online behavior, search activities on our Site and on other third party sites, and demographic information, so that the advertising you see on our site more closely reflects your interests and needs. For example, if you search for, or browse a, recipe or product on our site, you may see an advertisement from a third party with information about, or an offer similar to, that for which you were searching or browsing on our site, or an offer related to a third party whose site you have visited in the past. Tracking Options and California Do Not Track Disclosures Certain parts of our Site require cookies. You are free to set your Internet browser settings to stop accepting new cookies, to receive notice when you receive a new cookie, to disable existing cookies, and to omit images (which will disable pixel tags). On your mobile device, you may also adjust your privacy and advertising settings to control whether you want to receive more relevant advertising. By doing so, you may not be able to use certain features on the Site or take full advantage of all of our offerings. Please refer to your Web browser’s or operating system’s website or “Help” section for more information on how to disable your browser or operating system from receiving cookies or controlling your tracking preferences. Our system may not respond to Do Not Track requests or headers from some or all browsers. You can learn more about and opt out from receiving third party advertiser cookies by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out page here. Without cookies or pixel tags though, you may not be able to take full advantage of all of Kraft Heinz website features. We adhere to the Digital Advertising Alliance Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising. Information Collected From Other Sources We may obtain information about you from other sources, including commercially available sources, such as data aggregators and public databases, or social networks that you use to connect with us. This information may include your name, demographic information, interests, and publicly-observed data, such as from social media, online activity, and shopping behavior. We may combine this information with the information we collect from you to help us tailor our communications to you and to improve our services and products. How We Use Your Information We may use the information we collect from and about you to contact you from time to time, including for any of the following purposes:
To respond to your comments or questions, or contact you if needed while processing a product or service you requested through our website;
To improve our website, products, and services; develop new products or services; and conduct analysis to enhance current products and services; To review the usage and operations of our Site and improve our content, products; and services, including contacting you for your opinions on Kraft Heinz products, services, or websites;
To send you promotional offers, newsletter, materials, and other communications and information about Kraft Heinz, its portfolio of brands, affiliates, and its partners;
To provide you with content that is customized to your interests, targeted offers, and advertising on the Sites, on third party sites and media platforms, including in social media, or via email;
To contact you as necessary when you enter a contest, sweepstakes, or game in order to conduct the promotion (for example, to contact you if you’re a winner);
To contact you when necessary;
To use your data in an aggregated non-specific format for analytical and demographic purposes;
To address problems with the Site or our business;
To manage our telecommunications networks;
To protect the security or integrity of the Site and our business;
As otherwise described to you at the point of data collection; and To use and disclose your credit/debit card information only to process payments and prevent fraud.
Additionally, if you use the Site to connect with third party services you authorize us to use information from and about you, on your behalf, to interact with these third party services based on your requests. How We Share Your Information We do not sell or otherwise disclose personal information about our website visitors, except as described here. We do not share your personal information with unaffiliated third parties for their own marketing purposes without your consent. For California residents, please see “Your California Privacy Rights” below. We may share the information we collect from and about you in the following ways: (1) among Kraft Heinz brands and subsidiaries; (2) to our third party service providers we have retained to perform a business, professional or technical support functions for us, including to the extent necessary or desirable to help run promotions, fulfill orders, complete your transaction, or provide customer service (these service providers may have access to personal information about our Site visitors if it is needed to perform their functions for Kraft Heinz, but they are not authorized by Kraft Heinz to use or disclose the information except as necessary to perform services on Kraft Heinz’s behalf or to comply with legal requirements); (3) as necessary to investigate or prevent an actual or suspected crime or injury to ourselves or others, as permitted by law; (4) if we believe that there has been a violation of our Terms of Use or of our rights or the rights of any third party; (5) to respond to judicial process or provide information to law enforcement authorities, regulatory agencies, or other government officials, or otherwise as required by law; and (6) as otherwise described to you at the point of collection. In addition, we may share your email address with a third-party, such as a media agency, to send you interest-based advertising on our behalf. We may also share aggregated or de-identified information about you, including based on your email address, with our advertising and marketing partners, and third-party media platforms, including social media sites, to allow them to send targeted advertising messages and/or conduct analyses on our behalf. If you wish to stop receiving advertising messages from these third parties, please review the “Your Choices” section below. In addition, you may be able to opt out of these ads by clicking on an icon in the ad or through the privacy settings in each social media platform. We may conduct joint promotions with other companies. We may share with our promotional partners (and their service providers) certain personal information as necessary to conduct the promotion. We will not share this information with our promotional partners for any other purpose unless you consent to such sharing. During the normal course of our business, Kraft Heinz may sell or purchase assets. If another entity acquires us or any of our assets, information we have collected about you may be transferred to such entity. In addition, if any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding is brought by or against us, such information may be considered an asset of ours and may be sold or transferred to third parties. Should a sale or transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to try to require that the transferee use personal information provided through the Site in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Notice. Links To Other Websites The Sites may contain links to other websites. We provide these links solely for your convenience and information. Different websites have different privacy practices. You should always check the privacy notice of the specific site you’re visiting to understand the privacy practices associated with that site. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of third party websites. Public Forums Any information you may disclose on our Site, in blogs, on message boards, in chat rooms, or on other public areas on the Site or other third-party websites that this Site may link to, becomes public information. Please exercise caution when disclosing personal information in these public areas. Kraft Heinz cannot control the actions of third parties who may view the Site and use publicly-available information for their own purposes. Your Choices You can change your preferences for follow-up contacts by the Kraft Heinz Company. E-mail us if you wish to take this action or call us at the number listed in the “Contact Us” section below. If you wish to limit how third parties use your email address to send you targeted advertising through social media on our behalf, contact us here. Please allow 10 days for your email to be removed from our marketing database. Children's Information This site is intended for general audiences, and Kraft Heinz does not direct the Site to collect, or knowingly collect, any personal information from children under the age of 13. How We Protect Your Information The security of your information is important to us. We have taken certain administrative, technical, and physical steps to safeguard the information we collect from and about our customers and Site visitors against unauthorized use, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. While we make every effort to help ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee our security measures. Updates To This Privacy Notice We may change or update portions of this Privacy Notice at any time. When we do, we will post the change(s) on the Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to these terms means you accept these changes. Please check back from time to time so you are aware of any changes or updates to the notice. If we make any material changes, we will provide appropriate notice to you. We will indicate the notice’s effective date on the first page of the notice. How To Contact Us If you have any questions about this Privacy Notice, you can contact us at: The Kraft Heinz Company200 E. Randolph St. Chicago, IL 60601Attention: Consumer Relations1-800-543-53359 a.m. - 5 p.m. Eastern Time, Monday through Friday, excluding holidays. E-mail us. We would be happy to answer your questions or hear your concerns. California Privacy Rights Effective Date: January 1, 2020 Your privacy is important to us. This California Privacy Notice supplements our Website Privacy Notice and describes the types of information we collect from and about California residents when you visit any of our websites where this policy is posted (or the mobile optimized version of the website) (each a “Site”). This Privacy Notice also explains how we may use and disclose such information, as well as your ability to control certain uses of it. Please review our Website Privacy Notice for additional information about how we use your personal data. Any terms defined in the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (“CCPA”) have the same meeting when used in this California Privacy Notice. Information We Collect Information You Provide We collect certain personal information from you when you choose to share it with us. This personal information includes:
Category of Personal Information Examples
Identifiers Real name, postal address, IP address, email address, account name, social media account name
Characteristics of protected classifications under California or federal law Age, gender, race, ethnic background
Commercial information Records of products or services purchased, obtained, or considered; purchase histories
Internet or other electronic network activity information Page views, Site browsing history, information about your interaction with our Site
Professional or employment-related information Profession, job title, industry of employment, honorific
Education information Level of degree obtained
We do not collect the following categories of personal information using the Site:
biometric information, such as fingerprints or faceprints; geolocation data; or sensory data, such as audio, electronic, visual, thermal, or olfactory information.
Tracking Options and California Do Not Track Disclosures Certain parts of our Site require cookies. You are free to set your Internet browser settings to stop accepting new cookies, to receive notice when you receive a new cookie, to disable existing cookies, and to omit images (which will disable pixel tags). On your mobile device, you may also adjust your privacy and advertising settings to control whether you want to receive more relevant advertising. By doing so, you may not be able to use certain features on the Site or take full advantage of all of our offerings. Please refer to your Web browser’s or operating system’s website or “Help” section for more information on how to disable your browser or operating system from receiving cookies or controlling your tracking preferences. Our system may not respond to Do Not Track requests or headers from some or all browsers. You can learn more about and opt out from receiving third party advertiser cookies by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out page here. We adhere to the Digital Advertising Alliance Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising. How We Use and Share Your Information We use your personal information as described in the Website Privacy Notice.
We do not sell or otherwise disclose personal information about our website visitors except as described here. We do not share your personal information with unaffiliated third parties for their own marketing purposes without your consent. Please see “Your Rights and Choices” below for information on how to opt out of the sale of your data. We may share the information we collect from and about you in the following ways: (1) among Kraft Heinz brands and subsidiaries; (2) to our third party service providers we have retained to perform business, professional or technical support functions for us, including to the extent necessary or desirable to help run promotions, fulfill orders, complete your transaction, or provide customer service as described below (these service providers may have access to personal information about our Site visitors if it is needed to perform their functions for Kraft Heinz, but they are not authorized by Kraft Heinz to use or disclose the information except as necessary to perform services on Kraft Heinz’s behalf or to comply with legal requirements); (3) as necessary to investigate or prevent an actual or suspected crime or injury to ourselves or others, as permitted by law; (4) if we believe that there has been a violation of our Terms of Use or of our rights or the rights of any third party; (5) to respond to judicial process or provide information to law enforcement authorities, regulatory agencies, or other government officials, or otherwise as required by law; and (6) as otherwise described to you at the point of collection. We may share personal information we collect from and about you with our third-party service providers for the following business purposes:
To assist us in responding to your comments or questions, or contacting you if needed while processing a product or service you requested through our website; To improve our website, products, and services; develop new products or services; and conduct analysis to enhance current products and services; To review the usage and operations of our Site and improve our content, products; and services; To send you promotional offers, newsletters, materials, and other communications and information about Kraft Heinz, its portfolio of brands, affiliates, and its partners; To provide you with content that is customized to your interests, targeted offers, and advertising on the Sites, on third party sites and media platforms, including in social media, or via email, depending on your preferences; To contact you as necessary when you enter a contest, sweepstakes, or game in order to conduct the promotion (for example, to contact you if you’re a winner); To conduct joint promotions with third-party partners, where such personal information is necessary to conduct the promotion; To address problems with the Site or our business; To manage our telecommunications networks; To protect the security or integrity of the Site and our business; As otherwise described to you at the point of data collection; and To process credit/debit card information where needed to process payments and prevent fraud.
Additionally, if you use the Site to connect with third-party services you authorize us to use information from and about you, on your behalf, to interact with these third-party services based on your requests. Your Rights and Choices You have the right to request that we provide certain information to you about how we collected and used your personal information during the previous 12 months. Specifically, you have the right to request:
The categories of personal information we collected about you; The categories of sources of personal information we collected about you; The business or commercial purpose(s) for which we collected or sold your personal information; and
The categories of third parties with which we share your personal information and, where such disclosures were for a business purpose, the personal information categories that each category of third-party recipients received and, where such disclosures were sales, the personal information categories purchased by each category of recipient; The specific pieces of personal information we collected about you.
You also have the right to request that we delete personal information we collected from you, subject to certain exceptions. How to Exercise Your Rights If you would like to exercise the rights set out above, please submit a verifiable consumer request to us via:
Email at:USprivacy@kraftheinz.com Phone at:1-855-634-1984
A verifiable consumer request must provide us adequate information to allow us to (1) reasonably verify that you are the individual whose personal information we collected (or an authorized representative) and (2) to understand your request so that we can process and respond to it. Please note that only you, or a person registered with the California Secretary of State that you authorize to act on your behalf, may submit a verifiable consumer request for your personal information. You may submit verifiable consumer requests on behalf of your minor children.
Once we have received and verified your request, we will send a confirmation of our receipt of your request and, within 45 days, either a copy of the requested information or confirmation of deletion, as applicable. If, for any reason, we are unable to fulfill your request, we will notify you and provide an explanation. Do Not Sell My Personal Information To opt out of the sale of your personal information, please call us at 1-855-634-1984 or send an email to USprivacy@kraftheinz.com. Updates To This California Privacy Notice We may change or update portions of this California Privacy Notice at any time. When we do, we will post the change(s) on the Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to these terms means you accept these changes. Please check back from time to time so you are aware of any changes or updates to the notice. If we make any material changes, we will provide appropriate notice to you. We will indicate the notice’s effective date at the top of the notice. How To Contact Us If you have any questions about this California Privacy Notice, you can contact us at: The Kraft Heinz Company200 E. Randolph St. Chicago, IL 60601Attention: Data Privacy TeamCall us at 1-855-634-19849 a.m. - 5 p.m. Eastern Time, Monday through Friday, excluding holidays. E-mail us at USprivacy@kraftheinz.com. We would be happy to answer your questions or hear your concerns.
Follow us:
A.1.
Contact Us Terms of Use Privacy Product Locator Do Not Sell My Personal Information
©2020 Kraft Foods H.J. Heinz Company Brands LLC. All Rights Reserved
